Guide to the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Lodge 751-A Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Lodge 751-A records
1976-1986
University of Washington Libraries Special Collections Box 352900 Seattle, WA 98195-2900
6186
6186-001
International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers.$bLodge 751-A
0.86 cubic feet (2 boxes)
Union records of assembly and production workers at the Boeing Company
International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers Local Lodge No. 751-A, established in 1941, represents assembly and production workers at the Boeing Company.
These records include materials related to union officer elections, financial reports, and meeting minutes.
No restrictions on access.
Donated by IAM District 751.
Personal Papers/Corporate Records; Labor History; Labor Unions
- INTERNATIONAL ASSOCIATION OF MACHINISTS AND AEROSPACE WORKERS LOCAL LODGE 751-A, 1976-1986; RECORD GROUP 1
  - Election records, 1978-1984 (Box-folder 1/1)
  - Election nomination cards, 1984 (Box-folder 1/2)
  - Election letters, 1984 (Box-folder 1/3)
  - Expense vouchers, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 1/4)
  - Monthly financial reports, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 1/5)
  - Minutes, 1976 (Box-folder 1/6)
  - Minutes, 1977 (Box-folder 1/7)
  - Minutes, 1978 (Box-folder 1/8)
  - Minutes, 1979 (Box-folder 1/9)
  - Minutes, 1980 (Box-folder 1/10)
  - Minutes, 1981 (Box-folder 2/1)
  - Minutes, 1982 (Box-folder 2/2)
  - Minutes, 1983 (Box-folder 2/3)
  - Minutes, 1984 (Box-folder 2/4)
  - Minutes, 1985 (Box-folder 2/5)
  - Minutes, 1986 (Box-folder 2/6)